非常好，做完这些让我们看看
All right, you're done. Lets look at the
解决方案。现在需要开始在抽象线程的
solution. We'll begin by adding a log tag
SyncAdapter中加入一个记录页面。既然这个抽象线程是在
into our abstract threaded SyncAdapter. Since this stuff
后台运行的。我们使用一个记录器是非常有帮助的
runs in the background, it's really helpful to have
我们最终还是希望能够在SyncAdapter没有被察觉的
some logging. Since we ultimately want to run
状态下运行我们的程序。
the SyncAdapter in undetected mode. Let's pull the location
query from our utility class. And then we
paste in the code from our existing sunshine service.
We'll have to patch a few things up. We'll have to call getContext to
get the current context, for example. Note that I copied over ad location at
the same time I copied over the primary function. And then finally, we'll fix
update weather to use the new helper
function in our SyncAdapter. Let's run this.